usinsuranceonline.com 2015-03-21

# Privacy Policy

Last revised 3/10/2014

**OUR COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACY**

**Introduction.** We want to make your experience online satisfying and safe. This site is owned and operated by All Web Leads, Inc., a Delaware corporation (collectively " _Company_ ," " _we_ " or " _us_ ") headquartered in Austin, Texas. We understand that you value your privacy. This privacy policy (" _Privacy Policy_ ") governs information that you provide to us and information that we gather from your use of this website  and mobile websites, and it tells you how we may collect, use, and share this information.

Except as described in this Privacy Policy, or unless we are given permission by you, we will not sell or disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties.

All Web Leads, Inc. has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [information@allwebleads.com](mailto:information@allwebleads.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint).

To view a list of these Certified All Web Leads sites, please visit [www.truste.com](http://www.truste.com/). To view a list of mobile websites that are certified by TRUSTe, please see the mobile validation page.

**Why do we collect your information?** We help consumers shop for insurance, discounted health plans and other related products by connecting consumers with insurance companies, insurance agents, discount program representatives and other vendors, including vendors who also help match consumers with insurance providers or other vendors (we refer to all of these as " _Providers_ ", and we sometimes refer to both consumers and Providers as our " _users_ "). Since we deal with many Providers, the more detailed information you provide to us, the more accurate a quote our Providers may help you locate. 

We do not ask you for, access or track any location based information from your mobile device at any time while using our mobile sites or services. 

**Newsletters.** If you elect to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter, you may opt-out at any time by following the instructions included in each newsletter.

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT**

**What do we collect and how do we use it?**  By clicking "Get My Quotes" you expressly authorize up to eight insurance companies or their agents or partner companies to contact you at the number and address provided with insurance quotes or to obtain additional information for such purpose, via live, prerecorded or autodialed calls, text messages or email. You understand that your signature is not a condition of purchasing any property, goods or services and that you may revoke your consent at any time.  You understand that the insurance companies or their agents or partner companies may confirm your information through the use of a consumer report, which may include your credit score and driving record. 

By clicking "Get My Quotes" you also agree to this Privacy Policy and consent to your receipt of insurance quote reminders and special promotions via email from: member@myinsurancequotefinder.com. If you no longer wish to receive promotional emails from us you may opt-out at any time by using the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of each email communication or contact us at [unsubscribe@allwebleads.com](mailto:unsubscribe@allwebleads.com).  You acknowledge that you have read and understand this website's Terms and Conditions, and you agree to be bound by them.  We are not responsible, and shall not be held liable, if a Provider or other third party to whom we have forwarded any of the information you submitted to us violates our Privacy Policy or such third party's own privacy policy (if any), or otherwise violates the law.

Our users may from time-to-time provide us with personally identifiable information. Personally identifiable information generally means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, your name, home address, telephone number, and email address.

Examples of personally identifiable information may include:

  * First and Last Name
  * Postal Address
  * Email Address
  * Phone Number
  * Driver's License Number*
  * Date of Birth

_* While not required, this information may be helpful in processing your request to receive insurance or other quotations._

Certain of our users requesting quotations for health insurance may also be asked to provide certain personal health information, such as:

  * Major Health Conditions
  * Prescription Medications you or a family member may be taking
  * Whether or not you have been hospitalized in the past 5 years
  * Whether or not you have been treated by a doctor for a major health condition in the past year

We process personally identifiable information as described herein and also for such purposes as:

  * To deliver our products and services to users, including the display of customized content and advertising;
  * To conduct research and analysis in order to maintain and improve our products and services;
  * Ensuring the technical functioning of our system and network;
  * To aid us in developing new services;
  * To alert you to product updates, special offers, updated information and other new services. (You may opt-out of these communications if you so choose.)
  * To contact you in response to your requests for information; and
  * To provide you quotes from up to 8 Providers who may contact you using the information you provide or to obtain additional information needed to provide quotes.

Further, we may aggregate information we receive from you and from our other users and may use or disclose such aggregate information to third parties in a manner that does not disclose any individual user's personally identifiable information.

**Affiliate Sign up.** If you wish to register as an affiliate we collect your name, company name, email address and phone number. We use this information for contacting potential affiliates to determine the potential for a business relationship. We do not disclose this information to third parties.

**IMPORTANT NOTICE REGARDING CONSUMER REPORT PRACTICES** AS STATED ABOVE, BY CLICKING "GET MY QUOTES" AND SEEKING A QUOTE REQUEST, YOU AUTHORIZE AND AGREE THAT A PROVIDER MAY OBTAIN ADDITIONAL BACKGROUND INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO PROVIDE YOU WITH YOUR REQUESTED INSURANCE QUOTE OR POLICY INFORMATION. FOR EXAMPLE, CONSUMER AND/OR CREDIT REPORTS, OR DRIVING RECORDS, MAY BE ORDERED IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR QUOTE REQUEST. THESE REPORTS MAY PROVIDE ADDITIONAL INFORMATION THAT MAY ASSIST PROVIDERS IN DETERMINING YOUR ELIGIBILITY FOR INSURANCE, DISCOUNT HEALTH PLANS OR OTHER PRODUCTS OR SERVICES, AND RATES THAT YOU MAY BE CHARGED. CONSUMER REPORTS MAY ALSO BE USED FOR UPDATES, RENEWALS, OR EXTENSIONS OF ANY INSURANCE YOU MAY OBTAIN. A PROVIDER MAY ALSO OBTAIN AND USE A CREDIT-BASED INSURANCE SCORE CONTAINED IN YOUR CREDIT REPORT. THIS INFORMATION MAY BE COMBINED BY A PROVIDER WITH INFORMATION YOU SUBMIT TO US, AND BY CLICKING SUBMIT AND SEEKING A QUOTE REQUEST, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU ARE PROVIDING YOUR WRITTEN PERMISSION TO OUR PROVIDERS TO OBTAIN YOUR CREDIT REPORT.

**USAGE TRACKING**

**Usage Data Generally.** Like many internet companies, we track website and service usage data to improve the services we offer and the security of your interaction with the site. We collect user traffic patterns throughout our website. This information is collected to help improve website flow and usability. In addition, we track click-through information, including IP addresses, to our website from the reports and emails we send to our users. This is done to gauge the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns, to discourage fraudulent use and to improve the security of our site and your interaction with the site.

**Cookies.** We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie will enable us to relate your use of this website to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. The only personally identifiable information a cookie can contain is information that you yourself supply. We do not store personally identifiable information in cookies. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other websites that are not owned by us. We may use cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). In addition, we may use encrypted cookies to authenticate the user on each page after the user logs onto any portion of our website requiring a login. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you have set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. Some of our features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

The use of cookies by our third-party partners or affiliates is not covered by this Privacy Policy. We do not have access to or control over these cookies. Further, we and our partners, subsidiaries or affiliates may use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site(s).

**Clear GIFs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs).** Some of our third-party advertising partners employ a software technology called clear gifs (also called Web Beacons or Web Bugs) that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to any user's personally identifiable information.

**Mobile Analytics.** We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our Mobile Software on your phone.  This software may record information such as how often you use the mobile site, the events that occur within the mobile site, aggregated usage, performance data, and where the mobile site was accessed from.  We do not link the information we store within the analytics software to any personal information you submit within the mobile website.

**User Access.** We make a good-faith effort to enable you to update personally identifiable information you have provided to us and to enable you to request deletion of any of your information. If you wish to delete or update any of your personal information please email us at information@allwebleads.com . Please understand that while we are able to delete or update the information that we have received from you, this does not necessarily mean that information about you that has already been shared by us with other Providers may, at the same time, be updated or deleted by such other Providers. So, in some cases it may be necessary for you to contact other third parties who may have received your information and separately request updates to or deletions of your information. We may decline to process user requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, would be extremely impractical, or where information is required to be retained by us, either by law or for legitimate business purposes. Further, if you are a marketing affiliate, you may login to your account at any time to correct, update or delete inaccuracies in your personal information.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at the email address listed above.  We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

To request removal of your personal information from our blog, community forum, or testimonials contact us at the email address listed above.  In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

**Social Media (Features) and Widgets**

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

**INFORMATION TRANSFER AND SHARING POLICY**

**Generally.** When you begin to provide personally identifiable information to us, you do so for the purpose of our sharing this information with Providers to provide you with the quotes you requested, and this information then becomes subject to each Provider's own privacy policy (if any). Federal and state laws provide limitations on the information practices of financial institutions such as insurance companies. Providers and others to whom we may forward your personally identifiable information may contact you with a quote by email, telephone, postal mail, or other forms of communication as permitted by law and you agree to receive such contacts when you submit your information, regardless of the presence of your phone number(s) on any local or national no-call or similar no solicitation list. Except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy, we do not share personally identifiable information collected from you on this website with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Please understand that because we are in the business of helping consumers and Providers identify one another, if you are a consumer and you do not permit us to share your personally identifiable information with a Provider, we will be unable to assist you and certain of our services and offerings will be unavailable to you. We expect our Providers to whom we forward your information to follow applicable laws and abide by the restrictions we impose on their use of your personally identifiable information.

**Other Usage and Offerings.** As our business grows, from time to time we may seek to make available additional offerings and services including those that may not be insurance-related. In doing so, we will strive to give our users choices about whether or not you would like to continue to receive future promotional or marketing communications from us either directly or on behalf of others whose offerings we think may be of interest to you. In identifying which offerings we think may be of interest to you, we may use and analyze information you have provided to us. If you choose not to receive such marketing communications, you may still receive certain relationship or transactional communications from us as described herein. We do not plan to sell, rent or transfer your personally identifiable information for non-insurance related purposes to any third parties unless or except in connection with the merger, sale or reorganization of our business as set forth elsewhere in this policy.

**Vendors and Suppliers.** We may provide personally identifiable information to or permit access to personally identifiable information by our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, vendors and service providers for the purpose of verifying data or where such access is incidental to their assisting us such as phone number verification services and email service providers. We expect that these parties will only process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

**Protecting Our Legal Rights and Other's Rights.** We do not otherwise share personally identifiable information about website users with third parties unless we believe using or sharing such information is appropriate to carry out a user's request or if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce our [Terms and Conditions of Use](http://www.usinsuranceonline.com/terms.php), including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of the Company, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law or when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a legal or judicial proceeding or court order.

**Merger or Sale of Company.** If we should ever file for bankruptcy or have our assets sold to or merged with another entity, information that we receive from you through this website may be treated as an asset of the Company and may be transferred to the fullest extent permitted by law.

**Promotions and Programs.** From time to time, you may be given the opportunity to participate in sweepstakes, contests, giveaways, or other promotions and programs offered by us, either alone or with promotional partners. Participation in these promotions or programs may require you to submit additional information about yourself, including personally identifiable information. Our use and sharing of your information, including personally identifiable information, collected through a promotion or program will be governed by the official rules or agreement governing that promotion or program, as well as by this Privacy Policy. The terms of those rules or that agreement will supersede any conflicting provisions of this Privacy Policy.

**MARKETING AND OTHER COMMUNICATIONS**

When you submit information to us, you agree to receive email, fax, and other forms of communications from us and those to whom you have authorized us to forward your personally identifiable information. If you would like to opt-out of receiving promotional or marketing material from us in the future, please click the following link: [UNSUBSCRIBE](http://allwebleads.awlusc.com/dab4ad6f24c51694c2d892f5d8608944): or by following the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of each promotional or marketing email communication. Your decision to opt-out shall not preclude us from communicating with you regarding your existing or past relationship with us and shall not preclude us, including our employees, contractors and other representatives, from accessing and using the information you have provided in a manner that is not personally identifying (such as in aggregate or anonymous form). If you do not wish to receive further communications from any person or entity (such as a Provider) to whom we have forwarded your information with your permission, you must contact them directly.

**AFFILIATED WEBSITES, OTHER WEBSITES, AND ADVERTISEMENTS**

This Privacy Policy applies to websites and services that are owned and operated by All Web Leads, Inc. We do not exercise control over the websites of third parties that you may link to or view as part of a frame on a page on this website. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data, or solicit personally identifiable information from you. We are not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party. You should always be careful in how you use and share any sensitive personal information with any third party.

**BLOG**

If you use a blog on any of our sites, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected or used by other users of these blogs, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for any information you choose to submit in these blogs.

**CUSTOMER TESTIMONIALS/REVIEWS**

We post customer testimonials/reviews on our sites, which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the providing customer's consent prior to posting any such testimonial/review.

**AUTHORIZED USERS**

This website is hosted in the United States and is intended exclusively for U.S. residents. In using this website you represent and warrant that you have any and all necessary authorization to submit the information contained in your requests, and that you expressly consent to the transfer, use, and forwarding by us of the information you provide to us through the website and to the United States.

**SECURITY**

No data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure security on our systems. We use secure server software and firewalls as part of our efforts to protect your information from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software. By using our site, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to assume these risks.

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as social security number, Driver's license number, national ID, personal health information) on our registration forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

If we learn of a security systems breach, we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. By using this website or providing personally identifiable information to us you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy and administrative issues relating to your use of this website. We may post a notice on our website if a security breach occurs. We may also send an email to you at the email address you have provided to us in these circumstances. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us by clicking the following link: [Privacy Support](mailto:information@allwebleads.com).

**CHANGES AND UPDATES**

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy, and we expect that most such changes will be minor. When we make changes, we will also revise the "revised date" on the Privacy Policy. If we should decide to change this Privacy Policy in a manner that we believe would cause us to use or share your previously provided personally identifiable information in a way that we think is materially broader or less privacy-friendly from what we have told you here, we will make reasonable efforts to obtain your consent. To do this we may notify you on our homepage or this policy, by email or using other means and technology we think are appropriate given the changes. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed about how we are protecting the personally identifiable information we collect. Your submission of a quote request and/or other use of this website constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.

**CONTACTING US**

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about us or this Privacy Policy, please contact us by clicking the following link: [Information](mailto:information@allwebleads.com), by phone at (512) 279-3113, or by U.S. mail at 7300 FM 2222, Bldg. 2, Suite 100, Austin, TX 78730, Attention: Customer Service.
